Save the due date.
Knocked Up is a comedy, romance, drama film directed by Judd Apatow.
A slacker and a career-driven woman accidentally
conceive a child after a one-night stand.
As they try to make the relationship work, they must navigate the challenges
of parenthood and their differences in lifestyle and maturity.
Ben Stone, played by Seth Rogen.
Alison Scott, played by Katherine Heigl.
Pete, played by Paul Rudd.
Debbie, played by Leslie Mann.
Jason, played by Jason Segel.
Jay, played by Jay Baruchel.
Knocked Up is a 2007 American romantic comedy film written, produced and directed by Judd Apatow, and starring Seth
Rogen, Katherine Heigl, Paul Rudd, Leslie Mann, Jay Baruchel, Jonah Hill, Jason Segel and Martin Starr.
It follows the repercussions of a drunken one-night stand between a slacker and a
recently promoted media personality that results in an unintended pregnancy.
Knocked Up was directed by Apatow, from a screenplay by himself.
Apatow, Shauna Robertson and Clayton Townsend were involved in the film
as producers for the film studio, Apatow Productions.
Rogen and Evan Goldberg were involved in the film as executive producers.
Filming began in May 2006, in various locations in the United States, with a
focus on California, including Los Angeles and Santa Monica.
The cinematography was in charge of Eric Edwards, while the soundtrack
was composed by Loudon Wainwright III and Joe Henry.
The film was edited by Brent White and Craig Alpert.
The film had a budget of $25 million.
Knocked Up premiered at South by Southwest on March 12, 2007, and was released
in the United States on June 1, 2007, by Universal Pictures.
The film was a box office success, grossing $219 million
worldwide, and received positive reviews from critics.
This Is 40, a "sort-of sequel" focused on Rudd's and Mann's characters with Apatow
returning as writer/director, was released on December 21, 2012.
The film explores themes of alcohol, pregnancy, bed, one-night stand, condom.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.